<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Module>
<ModulePrefs title="hello world example" />
<Content type="html">
<![CDATA[
<!DOCTYPE html>
<html>
<head>
<title>Quote of the Day</title>
</head>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://ajax.googleapis.com/ajax/libs/jquery/1.9.1/jquery.min.js"></script>
<script src="jquery-csv.js"></script>
<script>

</script>
<body style="background-color: #F2F2F2">

<table style="border-collapse: collapse;height:94vh;background-color: #F2F2F2;" align="center" border="0" width="100%" bgcolor="#E8E8E8" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
<tr><td align="center" width="100%" height="100%" style="color: #BA371B;">

<script>

var now = new Date();
var start = new Date(now.getFullYear(), 0, 0);
var diff = now - start;
var oneDay = 1000 * 60 * 60 * 24;
var day = Math.floor(diff / oneDay);
console.log('Day of year: ' + day);

var Qoutes = [
{id:"1",quote:"A bird doesn't sing because it has an answer, it sings because it has a song.",author:"Maya Angelou"},
{id:"2",quote:"A champion is afraid of losing. Everyone else is afraid of winning.",author:"Billie Jean King"},
{id:"3",quote:"A collection of rare thoughts is nothing less than a cabinet of intellectual gems.",author:"William B. Sprague"},
{id:"4",quote:"A creative man is motivated by the desire to achieve, not by the desire to beat others.",author:"Ayn Rand"},
{id:"5",quote:"A goal is not always meant to be reached. It often serves simply as something to aim at.",author:"Bruce Lee"},
{id:"6",quote:"A great many people think they are thinking when they are merely rearranging their prejudices.",author:"William James"},
{id:"7",quote:"A hero is no braver than an ordinary man, but he is braver five minutes longer.",author:"Ralph Waldo Emerson"},
{id:"8",quote:"A leader is one who knows the way, goes the way, and shows the way.",author:"John C. Maxwell"},
{id:"9",quote:"A leader must have the courage to act against an expert's advice.",author:"James Callaghan"},
{id:"10",quote:"A leader who doesn't hesitate before he sends his nation into battle is not fit to be a leader.",author:"Golda Meir"},
{id:"11",quote:"A life of frustration is inevitable for any coach whose main enjoyment is winning.",author:"Chuck Noll"},
{id:"12",quote:"A man can succeed at almost anything for which he has unlimited enthusiasm.",author:"Charles Schwab"},
{id:"13",quote:"A man is not finished when he is defeated. He is finished when he quits.",author:"Richard Nixon"},
{id:"14",quote:"A mediocre idea that generates enthusiasm will go farther than a great idea that inspires no one.",author:"Mary Kay Ash"},
{id:"15",quote:"A ship in harbour is safe, but that is not what ships are built for.",author:"William Shedd"},
{id:"16",quote:"A successful man is one who can lay a firm foundation with the bricks others have thrown at him.",author:"David Brinkley"},
{id:"17",quote:"A wise man can see more from the bottom of a well than a fool can from a mountain top.",author:"Unknown"},
{id:"18",quote:"Ability may get you to the top, but it takes character to keep you there.",author:"John Wooden"},
{id:"19",quote:"All endings are also beginnings. We just don't know it at the time.",author:"Mitch Albom"},
{id:"20",quote:"All our dreams can come true ? if we have the courage to pursue them.",author:"Walt Disney"},
{id:"21",quote:"All you need is ignorance and confidence and the success is sure.",author:"Mark Twain"},
{id:"22",quote:"Always bear in mind that your own resolution to succeed is more important than any other.",author:"Abraham Lincoln"},
{id:"23",quote:"Always do your best. What you plant now, you will harvest later.",author:"Og Mandino"},
{id:"24",quote:"Always remember that striving and struggle precede success, even in the dictionary.",author:"Sarah Ban Breathnach"},
{id:"25",quote:"And now, this is the sweetest and most glorious day that ever my eyes did see.",author:"Donald Cargill"},
{id:"26",quote:"Anyone who has never made a mistake has never tried anything new.",author:"Albert Einstein"},
{id:"27",quote:"As a young athlete, it was first about having fun;then it was about winning.",author:"Dan O'Brien"},
{id:"28",quote:"Authority without wisdom is like a heavy axe without an edge, fitter to bruise than polish.",author:"Anne Bradstreet"},
{id:"29",quote:"Be enthusiastic as a leader. You can't light a fire with a wet match.",author:"Unknown"},
{id:"30",quote:"Be miserable. Or motivate yourself. Whatever has to be done, it's always your choice.",author:"Wayne Dyer"},
{id:"31",quote:"Being nominated is the win. For me, being nominated is winning. It's just unbelievable.",author:"Martha Plimpton"},
{id:"32",quote:"Being powerful is like being a lady. If you have to tell people you are, you arenft!",author:"Margaret Thatcher"},
{id:"33",quote:"Belief in oneself is one of the most important bricks in building any successful venture.",author:"Lydia M. Child"},
{id:"34",quote:"Believe with all of your heart that you will do what you were made to do.",author:"Orison Swett Marden"},
{id:"35",quote:"Big jobs usually go to the men who prove their ability to outgrow small ones.",author:"Ralph Waldo Emerson"},
{id:"36",quote:"Big pay and little responsibility are circumstances seldom found together.",author:"Napoleon Hill"},
{id:"37",quote:"Boys, baseball is a game where you gotta have fun. You do that by winning.",author:"Dave Bristol"},
{id:"38",quote:"Character may be manifested in the great moments, but it is made in the small ones.",author:"Phillips Brooks"},
{id:"39",quote:"Coming together is a beginning; keeping together is progress; working together is success.",author:"Henry Ford"},
{id:"40",quote:"Confidence comes not from always being right but not fearing to be wrong.",author:"Peter T. Mcintyre"},
{id:"41",quote:"Courage is going from failure to failure without losing enthusiasm.",author:"Winston Churchill"},
{id:"42",quote:"Courage is the discovery that you may not win, and trying when you know you can lose.",author:"Tom Crause"},
{id:"43",quote:"Crave for a thing, you will get it. Renounce the craving, the object will follow you by itself.",author:"Swami Sivananda"},
{id:"44",quote:"Death is more universal than life; everyone dies but not everyone lives.",author:"A. Sachs"},
{id:"45",quote:"Defeat is not the worst of failures. Not to have tried is the true failure.",author:"George Edward Woodberry"},
{id:"46",quote:"Definiteness of purpose is the starting point of all achievement.",author:"W. Clement Stone"},
{id:"47",quote:"Difficulties are meant to rouse, not discourage. The human spirit is to grow strong by conflict.",author:"William E. Channing"},
{id:"48",quote:"Divorced from ethics, leadership is reduced to management and politics to mere technique.",author:"James MacGregor Burns"},
{id:"49",quote:"Do not go where the path may lead, go instead where there is no path and leave a trail.",author:"Ralph Waldo Emerson"},
{id:"50",quote:"Do not wait to strike till the iron is hot; but make it hot by striking.",author:"William B. Sprague"},
{id:"51",quote:"Do you want to know who you are? Don't ask. Act! Action will delineate and define you.",author:"Thomas Jefferson"},
{id:"52",quote:"Do your work with your whole heart, and you will succeed - there's so little competition.",author:"Elbert Hubbard"},
{id:"53",quote:"Don't be discouraged. It's often the last key in the bunch that opens the lock.",author:"Unknown"},
{id:"54",quote:"Don't compare your life to others. You have no idea what their journey is all about.",author:"Unknown"},
{id:"55",quote:"Don't give up at half time. Concentrate on winning the second half.",author:"Paul Bryant"},
{id:"56",quote:"Don't judge each day by the harvest you reap but by the seeds that you plant.",author:"Robert Louis Stevenson"},
{id:"57",quote:"Don't judge those who try and fail, judge those who fail to try.",author:"Unknown"},
{id:"58",quote:"Enthusiasm is that secret and harmonious spirit which hovers over the production of genius.",author:"Isaac Disraeli"},
{id:"59",quote:"Enthusiasm is the greatest asset in the world. It beats money, power and influence",author:"Henry Chester"},
{id:"60",quote:"Even as empiricism is winning the mind, transcendentalism continues to win the heart.",author:"E. O. Wilson"},
{id:"61",quote:"Even if I knew that tomorrow the world would go to pieces, I would still plant my apple tree.",author:"Martin Luther"},
{id:"62",quote:"Every leader needs to look back once in a while to make sure he has followers.",author:"Unknown"},
{id:"63",quote:"Every moment and every event of every man's life on earth plants something in his soul.",author:"Thomas Merton"},
{id:"64",quote:"Everyone talks about age, but it's not about age. It's about work ethic. Winning never gets old.",author:"Lisa Leslie"},
{id:"65",quote:"Everything will be OK in the end, if it's not OK, it's not the end.",author:"Unknown"},
{id:"66",quote:"Everytime you are not practicing, someone else is...when you play them, they will win.",author:"Unknown"},
{id:"67",quote:"Example is not the main thing in influencing others.  It is the only thing.",author:"Albert Schweitzer"},
{id:"68",quote:"Experience is not what happens to you; it is what you do with what happens to you.",author:"Aldous Huxley"},
{id:"69",quote:"Failure is only the opportunity to begin again, this time more wisely.",author:"Unknown"},
{id:"70",quote:"Failure is the key to success;each mistake teaches us something.",author:"Morihei Ueshiba"},
{id:"71",quote:"Find a place inside where there's joy, and the joy will burn out the pain.",author:"Joseph Campbell"},
{id:"72",quote:"For me, victory isn't measured by winning in the traditional sense.",author:"Dinesh D'Souza"},
{id:"73",quote:"For true success ask yourself these four questions: Why? Why not? Why not me? Why not now?",author:"James Allen"},
{id:"74",quote:"Formal education will make you a living;self-education will make you a fortune.",author:"Jim Rohn"},
{id:"75",quote:"Frustration, although quite painful at times, is a very positive and essential part of success.",author:"Bo Bennett"},
{id:"76",quote:"Great spirits have always encountered violent opposition from mediocre minds.",author:"Albert Einstein"},
{id:"77",quote:"Great things are done by a series of small things brought together.",author:"Vincent van Gogh"},
{id:"78",quote:"Great works are performed not by strength, but by perseverance.",author:"Samuel Johnson"},
{id:"79",quote:"Happiness is a perfume you cannot pour on others without getting a few drops on yourself.",author:"Ralph Waldo Emerson"},
{id:"80",quote:"Happiness is not something you postpone for the future;it is something you design for the present.",author:"Jim Rohn"},
{id:"81",quote:"Happiness lies in the joy of achievement and the thrill of creative effort.",author:"Franklin D. Roosevelt"},
{id:"82",quote:"Happiness resides not in possessions, and not in gold, happiness dwells in the soul.",author:"Democritus"},
{id:"83",quote:"Happy are those who dream dreams and are ready to pay the price to make them come true.",author:"Leon J. Suenes"},
{id:"84",quote:"He that is good for making excuses is seldom good for anything else.",author:"Benjamin Franklin"},
{id:"85",quote:"He who speaks without modesty will find it difficult to make his words good.",author:"Confucius"},
{id:"86",quote:"Hope is like the sun, which, as we journey toward it, casts the shadow of our burden behind us.",author:"Samuel Smiles"},
{id:"87",quote:"Hope, like faith, is nothing if it is not courageous;it is nothing if it is not ridiculous.",author:"Thornton Wilder"},
{id:"88",quote:"How a man plays a game shows something of his character, how he loses shows all of it.",author:"Unknown"},
{id:"89",quote:"I am always doing that which I cannot do, in order that I may learn how to do it.",author:"Pablo Picasso"},
{id:"90",quote:"I can't change the direction of the wind, but I can adjust my sails to always reach my destination.",author:"Jimmy Dean"},
{id:"91",quote:"I do not think that winning is the most important thing. I think winning is the only thing.",author:"Bill Veeck"},
{id:"92",quote:"I don't believe in failure. It's not failure if you enjoyed the process.",author:"Oprah Winfrey"},
{id:"93",quote:"I don't know the key to success, but the key to failure is trying to please everybody.",author:"Bill Cosby"},
{id:"94",quote:"I don't measure a man's success by how high he climbs but how high he bounces when he hits bottom.",author:"George S. Patton"},
{id:"95",quote:"I have failed over and over gain in my life and that is why I succeed.",author:"Michael Jordan"},
{id:"96",quote:"I have looked into your eyes with my eyes. I have put my heart near your heart.",author:"Pope John XXIII"},
{id:"97",quote:"I love the winning, I can take the losing, but most of all I Love to play.",author:"Boris Becker"},
{id:"98",quote:"I mean, I love winning, but losing is a much more intense feeling.",author:"Jennie Finch"},
{id:"99",quote:"I suppose that leadership at one time meant muscle; but today it means getting along with people.",author:"Indira Gandhi"},
{id:"100",quote:"I was a fighter and very determined. There was no way I was going to back out without winning.",author:"Christine Lahti"},
{id:"101",quote:"I was motivated to be different in part because I was different.",author:"Donna Brazile"},
{id:"102",quote:"I'd rather attempt to do something great and fail than to attempt to do nothing and succeed.",author:"Robert H. Schuller"},
{id:"103",quote:"If everyone is moving forward together, then success takes care of itself.",author:"Henry Ford"},
{id:"104",quote:"If I have seen farther than others, it is because I was standing on the shoulder of giants.",author:"Issac Newton"},
{id:"105",quote:"If the whole world followed you, would you be pleased with where you took it?",author:"Neale Donald Walsch"},
{id:"106",quote:"If the wind will not serve,take to the oars.Destitutus ventis, remos adhibe",author:"Latin Proverb"},
{id:"107",quote:"If we did all the things we are capable of, we would astound ourselves.",author:"Thomas Edison"},
{id:"108",quote:"If you are not big enough to lose, you are not big enough to win.",author:"Walter Reuther"},
{id:"109",quote:"If you ask me what I came into this life to do, I will tell you: I came to live out loud.",author:"Emile Zola"},
{id:"110",quote:"If you do not do the thing you fear, the fear controls your life.",author:"Brian Tracy"},
{id:"111",quote:"If you do not hope, you will not find what is beyond your hopes.",author:"St. Clement of Alexandra"},
{id:"112",quote:"If you don't think every day is a good day, just try missing one.",author:"Cavett Robert"},
{id:"113",quote:"If you really want something, you can figure out how to make it happen.",author:"Cher"},
{id:"114",quote:"If you think you can, you can. And if you think you can't, you're right.",author:"Henry Ford"},
{id:"115",quote:"If you want to conquer fear, don't sit home and think about it. Go out and get busy.",author:"Dale Carnegie"},
{id:"116",quote:"If you want to test your memory, try to recall what you were worrying about one year ago today.",author:"E. Joseph Cossman"},
{id:"117",quote:"In matters of style, swim with the current; in matters of principle, stand like a rock.",author:"Thomas Jefferson"},
{id:"118",quote:"In order to succeed you must fail, so that you know what not to do the next time.",author:"Anthony J. D'Angelo"},
{id:"119",quote:"In order to succeed, your desire for success should be greater than your fear of failure.",author:"Bill Cosby"},
{id:"120",quote:"In taking revenge, a man is but even with his enemy; but in passing it over, he is superior.",author:"Sir Francis Bacon"},
{id:"121",quote:"In the end, the size of a person's accomplishment can best be measured by the size of their heart.",author:"Unknown"},
{id:"122",quote:"In the long run the pessimist may be proved right, but the optimist has a better time on the trip.",author:"Daniel L. Reardon"},
{id:"123",quote:"In the long run, men hit only what they aim at. Therefore, they had better aim at something high.",author:"Henry David Thoreau"},
{id:"124",quote:"In this world it is not what we take up, but what we give up, that makes us rich.",author:"Henry Ward Beecher"},
{id:"125",quote:"Inside my empty bottle I was constructing a lighthouse while all the others were making ships.",author:"Charles Simic"},
{id:"126",quote:"Instead of giving myself reasons why I can't, I give myself reasons why I can.",author:"Unknown"},
{id:"127",quote:"It doesn't matter where you are coming from. All that matters is where you are going.",author:"Brian Tracy"},
{id:"128",quote:"It hasn't been hard getting nominated, but winning it is another thing. The competition is tough.",author:"Gary Burton"},
{id:"129",quote:"It is amazing how much people can get done if they do not worry about who gets the credit.",author:"Sandra Swinney"},
{id:"130",quote:"It is better to know some of the questions than all of the answers.",author:"James Thurber"},
{id:"131",quote:"It is during our darkest moments that we must focus to see the light.",author:"Aristotle Onassis"},
{id:"132",quote:"It is literally true that you can succeed best and quickest by helping others to succeed.",author:"Napoleon Hill"},
{id:"133",quote:"It is no use saying, 'We are doing our best.' You have got to succeed in doing what is necessary.",author:"Winston Churchill"},
{id:"134",quote:"It is not ignorance but knowledge which is the mother of wonder.",author:"Joseph Wood Krutch"},
{id:"135",quote:"It is on our failures that we base a new and different and better success.",author:"Havelock Ellis"},
{id:"136",quote:"It is only in sorrow bad weather masters us;in joy we face the storm and defy it.",author:"Amelia Barr"},
{id:"137",quote:"It's a helluva start being able to recognize what makes you happy.",author:"Lucille Ball"},
{id:"138",quote:"It's about lessons for life. It's not just about winning either.",author:"Lynn Davies"},
{id:"139",quote:"It's fool's gold if you are winning games and are not playing the right way.",author:"Antonio Davis"},
{id:"140",quote:"It's not that I'm so smart, it's just that I stay with problems longer.",author:"Albert Einstein"},
{id:"141",quote:"It's not the size of the dog in the fight, but the size of the fight in the dog.",author:"Mark Twain"},
{id:"142",quote:"It's not who you are that holds you back, it's who you think you're not.",author:"Unknown"},
{id:"143",quote:"It's not winning or losing. It's the friends and the people that you meet along the way.",author:"Summer Altice"},
{id:"144",quote:"It's our nature: Human beings like success but they hate successful people.",author:"Carrot Top"},
{id:"145",quote:"I've never been in a place where winning has hurt the ability to do anything.",author:"Rahm Emanuel"},
{id:"146",quote:"Joy descends gently upon us like the evening dew, and does not patter down like a hailstorm.",author:"Jean Paul"},
{id:"147",quote:"Just because something is easy to measure doesn't mean it's important.",author:"Seth Godin"},
{id:"148",quote:"Keep steadily before you the fact that all true success depends at last upon yourself.",author:"Theodore T. Hunger"},
{id:"149",quote:"Keep your fears to yourself, but share your inspiration with others.",author:"Robert Louis Stevenson"},
{id:"150",quote:"Knowing is not enough; we must apply. Willing is not enough; we must do.",author:"Johann Wolfgang von Goethe"},
{id:"151",quote:"Laugh when you can, apologize when should, and let go of what you can't change.",author:"Unknown"},
{id:"152",quote:"Leaders are more powerful role models when they learn than when they teach.",author:"Rosabeth Moss Kantor"},
{id:"153",quote:"Leaders must be close enough to relate to others, but far enough ahead to motivate them.",author:"John Maxwell"},
{id:"154",quote:"Leaders need to be optimists.  Their vision is beyond the present.",author:"Rudy Giuliani"},
{id:"155",quote:"Leadership involves finding a parade and getting in front of it.",author:"John Naisbitt"},
{id:"156",quote:"Leadership should be more participative than directive, more enabling than performing.",author:"Mary D. Poole"},
{id:"157",quote:"Life is like riding a bicycle. To keep your balance you must keep moving.",author:"Albert Einstein"},
{id:"158",quote:"Life is what happens to you while your'e busy making other plans",author:"John Lennon"},
{id:"159",quote:"Live as if you were to die tomorrow. Learn as if you were to live forever.",author:"Mahatma Gandhi"},
{id:"160",quote:"Logic will get you from A to B. Imagination will take you everywhere.",author:"Albert Einstein"},
{id:"161",quote:"London 2012 is all about winning a medal. Not just any medal, the gold medal.",author:"Hope Solo"},
{id:"162",quote:"Look within. Within is the fountain of good, and it will ever bubble up, if thou wilt ever dig.",author:"Marcus Aurelius"},
{id:"163",quote:"Losers visualize the penalties of failure. Winners visualize the rewards of success.",author:"Rob Gilbert"},
{id:"164",quote:"Man needs his difficulties because they are necessary to enjoy success.",author:"Abdul Kalam"},
{id:"165",quote:"Management is doing things right; leadership is doing the right things.",author:"Peter Drucker"},
{id:"166",quote:"Many ideas grow better when transplanted into another mind, than in the one where they sprung up.",author:"Oliver Wendell Holmes"},
{id:"167",quote:"Men succeed when they realize that their failures are the preparation for their victories.",author:"Ralph Waldo Emerson"},
{id:"168",quote:"Men take only their needs into consideration, never their abilities.",author:"Napoleon Bonaparte"},
{id:"169",quote:"Mistakes are always forgivable, if one has the courage to admit them.",author:"Bruce Lee"},
{id:"170",quote:"Most people would rather be certain they're miserable, than risk being happy.",author:"Robert Anthony"},
{id:"171",quote:"Motivation is the art of getting people to do what you want them to do because they want to do it.",author:"Dwight D. Eisenhower"},
{id:"172",quote:"My great concern is not whether you have failed, but whether you are content with your failure.",author:"Abraham Lincoln"},
{id:"173",quote:"My peers say I have made a difference. That means more to me than winning an Oscar.",author:"Conrad Hall"},
{id:"174",quote:"Nature magically suits a man to his fortunes, by making them the fruit of his character.",author:"Ralph Waldo Emerson"},
{id:"175",quote:"Nearly all men can stand adversity, but if you want to test a man's character, give him power.",author:"Abraham Lincoln"},
{id:"176",quote:"Never apologize for showing feeling. When you do so, you apologize for the truth.",author:"Benjamin Disraeli"},
{id:"177",quote:"Never consider the possibility of failure; as long as you persist, you will be successful.",author:"Brian Tracy"},
{id:"178",quote:"Never give up, for that is just the place and time that the tide will turn.",author:"Harriett Beecher Stowe"},
{id:"179",quote:"Never let yesterday's disappointments overshadow tomorrow's dreams.",author:"Unknown"},
{id:"180",quote:"Never mistake knowledge for wisdom. One helps you make a living; the other helps you make a life.",author:"Sandra Carey"},
{id:"181",quote:"Never stop doing your best just because one person doesn't give you credit.",author:"Kamari"},
{id:"182",quote:"Ninety-nine percent of the failures come from people who have the habit of making excuses.",author:"George Washington Carver"},
{id:"183",quote:"No matter how many goals you have achieved, you must set your sights on a higher one.",author:"Jessica Savitch"},
{id:"184",quote:"No person who is enthusiastic about his work has anything to fear from life.",author:"Samuel Goldwyn"},
{id:"185",quote:"Nobody can go back and start a new beginning, but anyone can start today and make a new ending.",author:"Maria Robinson"},
{id:"186",quote:"Not doing more than the average is what keeps the average down.",author:"William Winans"},
{id:"187",quote:"Nothing is permanent in this wicked world - not even our troubles.",author:"Charlie Chaplin"},
{id:"188",quote:"Nothing will ever be attempted if all possible objections must first be overcome.",author:"Samuel Johnson"},
{id:"189",quote:"Now that it's all over, what did you really do yesterday that's worth mentioning?",author:"Coleman Cox"},
{id:"190",quote:"Nurture your minds with great thoughts. To believe in the heroic makes heroes.",author:"Benjamin Disraeli"},
{id:"191",quote:"Once you say you're going to settle for second, that's what happens to you in life.",author:"John F. Kennedy"},
{id:"192",quote:"One doesn't discover new lands without consenting to lose sight of the shore for a very long time.",author:"Andre Gide"},
{id:"193",quote:"One measure of leadership is the caliber of people who choose to follow you.",author:"Dennis A. Peer"},
{id:"194",quote:"One of the greatest weaknesses in most of us is our lack of faith in ourselves.",author:"L. Tom Perry"},
{id:"195",quote:"One of the secrets of life is to make stepping stones out of stumbling blocks.",author:"Jack Penn"},
{id:"196",quote:"One secret of success in life is for a man to be ready for his opportunity when it comes.",author:"Benjamin Disraeli"},
{id:"197",quote:"One way to keep momentum going is to have constantly greater goals.",author:"Michael Korda"},
{id:"198",quote:"Only those who will risk going too far can possibly find out how far one can go.",author:"T.S. Elliot"},
{id:"199",quote:"Opportunity does not knock, it presents itself when you beat down the door.",author:"Kyle Chandler"},
{id:"200",quote:"Opportunity is missed by most people because it is dressed in overalls and looks like work.",author:"Thomas Edison"},
{id:"201",quote:"Optimism is the faith that leads to achievement. Nothing can be done without hope and confidence.",author:"Helen Keller"},
{id:"202",quote:"Our lives begin to end the day we become silent about things that matter.",author:"Martin Luther King Jr"},
{id:"203",quote:"Patience, persistence and perspiration make an unbeatable combination for success.",author:"Napoleon Hill"},
{id:"204",quote:"Pay no attention to what the critics say;no statue has ever been erected to a critic.",author:"Jean Sibelius"},
{id:"205",quote:"People confuse being world No. 1 with winning a Major championship.",author:"Lee Westwood"},
{id:"206",quote:"People may doubt what you say, but they will believe what you do.",author:"Lewis Cass"},
{id:"207",quote:"People seem not to see that their opinion of the world is a confession of character.",author:"Ralph Waldo Emerson"},
{id:"208",quote:"Perseverance is not a long race;it is many short races one after the other.",author:"Walter Elliot"},
{id:"209",quote:"Picture yourself vividly as winning, and that alone will contribute immeasurably to success.",author:"Harry Emerson Fosdick"},
{id:"210",quote:"Placing the ball in the right position for the next shot is eighty percent of winning golf.",author:"Ben Hogan"},
{id:"211",quote:"Pray that success will not come any faster than you are able to endure it.",author:"Elbert Hubbard"},
{id:"212",quote:"Proverbs are mental gems gathered in the diamond districts of the mind.",author:"William R. Alger"},
{id:"213",quote:"Put your heart, mind, and soul into even your smallest acts. This is the secret of success.",author:"Swami Sivananda"},
{id:"214",quote:"Remember the difference between a boss and a leader; a boss says Go! a leader says Let's go!",author:"E.M. Kelly"},
{id:"215",quote:"Seek the lofty by reading, hearing and seeing great work at some moment every day.",author:"Thornton Wilder"},
{id:"216",quote:"Setting goals is the first step in turning the invisible into the visible.",author:"Tony Robbins"},
{id:"217",quote:"Shallow men believe in luck. Strong men believe in cause and effect.",author:"Ralph Waldo Emerson"},
{id:"218",quote:"Show class, have pride, and display character. If you do, winning takes care of itself.",author:"Paul Bryant"},
{id:"219",quote:"Some people want it to happen, some wish it would happen, others make it happen.",author:"Michael Jordan"},
{id:"220",quote:"Somebody will always break your records. It is how you live that counts.",author:"Earl Campbell"},
{id:"221",quote:"Someone's sitting in the shade today because someone planted a tree a long time ago.",author:"Warren Buffett"},
{id:"222",quote:"Stealing someone else's words frequently spares the embarrassment of eating your own.",author:"Peter Anderson"},
{id:"223",quote:"Success consists of going from failure to failure without loss of enthusiasm.",author:"Winston Churchill"},
{id:"224",quote:"Success does not consist in never making blunders, but in never making the same one a second time.",author:"Josh Billings"},
{id:"225",quote:"Success has a simple formula: do your best, and people may like it.",author:"Sam Ewing"},
{id:"226",quote:"Success is a lousy teacher. It seduces smart people into thinking they can't lose.",author:"Bill Gates"},
{id:"227",quote:"Success is a science;if you have the conditions, you get the result.",author:"Oscar Wilde"},
{id:"228",quote:"Success is focusing the full power of all you are on what you have a burning desire to achieve.",author:"Wilfred Peterson"},
{id:"229",quote:"Success is getting what you want. Happiness is wanting what you get.",author:"Dale Carnegie"},
{id:"230",quote:"Success is going from failure to failure without a loss of enthusiasm.",author:"Sir Winston Churchill"},
{id:"231",quote:"Success is not final, failure is not fatal: it is the courage to continue that counts.",author:"Winston Churchill"},
{id:"232",quote:"Success is often the result of taking a misstep in the right direction.",author:"Al Bernstein"},
{id:"233",quote:"Success is simple. Do what's right, the right way, at the right time.",author:"Arnold H. Glasgow"},
{id:"234",quote:"Success is the good fortune that comes from aspiration, desperation, perspiration and inspiration.",author:"Evan Esar"},
{id:"235",quote:"Success is the progressive realization of predetermined, worthwhile, personal goals.",author:"Paul J. Meyer"},
{id:"236",quote:"Success is the sum of small efforts, repeated day in and day out.",author:"Robert Collier"},
{id:"237",quote:"Success isn't a result of spontaneous combustion. You must set yourself on fire.",author:"Arnold H. Glasow"},
{id:"238",quote:"Success seems to be largely a matter of hanging on after others have let go.",author:"William Feather"},
{id:"239",quote:"Success to me is having ten honeydew melons and eating only the top half of each slice.",author:"Barbra Streisand"},
{id:"240",quote:"Successful leaders have the courage to take action while others hesitate.",author:"John Maxwell"},
{id:"241",quote:"That some achieve great success, is proof to all that others can achieve it as well.",author:"Abraham Lincoln"},
{id:"242",quote:"The best and fastest way to learn a sport is to watch and imitate a champion.",author:"Jean-Claude Killy"},
{id:"243",quote:"The best leaders are the best notetakers, best askers and best learners.",author:"They are shameless thieves."},
{id:"244",quote:"The best thing about the future is that it only comes one day at a time.",author:"Abraham Lincoln"},
{id:"245",quote:"The biggest thrill wasn't in winning on Sunday but in meeting the payroll on Monday.",author:"Art Rooney"},
{id:"246",quote:"The definition of madness is doing the same thing and excpecting a different result.",author:"Albert Einstein"},
{id:"247",quote:"The difference between the impossible and the possible lies in a person's determination.",author:"Tommy Lasorda"},
{id:"248",quote:"The difference between winning and losing is always a mental one.",author:"Peter Thomson"},
{id:"249",quote:"The distance between insanity and genius is measured only by success.",author:"Bruce Feirstein"},
{id:"250",quote:"The drops of rain make a hole in the stone, not by violence, but by oft falling.",author:"Lucretius"},
{id:"251",quote:"The entrepreneur always searches for change, responds to it, and exploits it as an opportunity.",author:"Peter Drucker"},
{id:"252",quote:"The fun never goes out, but it changes with the years, with winning and losing.",author:"Bear Bryant"},
{id:"253",quote:"The function of leadership is to produce more leaders, not more followers.",author:"Ralph Nader"},
{id:"254",quote:"The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams.",author:"Eleanor Roosevelt"},
{id:"255",quote:"The greatest mistake you can make in life is to continually be afraid you will make one.",author:"Elbert Hubbard"},
{id:"256",quote:"The greatest motivational act one person can do for another is to listen.",author:"Robert E. Moody"},
{id:"257",quote:"The greatest obstacle to discovery is not ignorance - it is the illusion of knowledge.",author:"Daniel J. Boorstin"},
{id:"258",quote:"The greatest pleasure in life is doing what people say you cannot do.",author:"Walter Bagehot"},
{id:"259",quote:"The hardships that I encountered in the past will help me succeed in the future.",author:"Philip Emeagwali"},
{id:"260",quote:"The key is to keep company only with people who uplift you, whose presence calls forth your best.",author:"Epictetus"},
{id:"261",quote:"The ladder of success is best climbed by stepping on the rungs of opportunity.",author:"Ayn Rand"},
{id:"262",quote:"The longer you play, the better chance the better player has of winning.",author:"Jack Nicklaus"},
{id:"263",quote:"The man who can drive himself further once the effort gets painful is the man who will win.",author:"Roger Bannister"},
{id:"264",quote:"The man who wants to lead the orchestra must turn his back on the crowd.",author:"James Crook"},
{id:"265",quote:"The meaning I picked, the one that changed my life: Overcome fear, behold wonder.",author:"Richard Bach"},
{id:"266",quote:"The momentous thing in human life is the art of winning the soul to good or evil.",author:"Francis Bacon"},
{id:"267",quote:"The more man meditates upon good thoughts, the better will be his world and the world at large.",author:"Confucius"},
{id:"268",quote:"The most important quality in a leader is that of being acknowledged as such.",author:"Andre Maurois"},
{id:"269",quote:"The most momentous thing in human life is the art of winning the soul to good or evil.",author:"Pythagoras"},
{id:"270",quote:"The one phrase you can use is that success has a thousand fathers, and failure is an orphan.",author:"Alan Price"},
{id:"271",quote:"The only limitations you will ever have are the ones you put on yourself.",author:"Kristinna Habashy"},
{id:"272",quote:"The only way of finding the limits of the possible is by going beyond them into the impossible.",author:"Arthur C. Clarke"},
{id:"273",quote:"The people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world are the ones who do.",author:"Apple"},
{id:"274",quote:"The person that said winning isn't everything, never won anything.",author:"Mia Hamm"},
{id:"275",quote:"The real leader has no need to lead he is content to point the way.",author:"Henry Miller, The Wisdom of the Heart"},
{id:"276",quote:"The real opportunity for success lies within the person and not in the job.",author:"Zig Ziglar"},
{id:"277",quote:"The secret of all those who make discoveries is that they regard nothing as impossible.",author:"Justus Liebig"},
{id:"278",quote:"The shepherd always tries to persuade the sheep that their interests and his own are the same.",author:"Henri B. Stendhal"},
{id:"279",quote:"The successful man will profit from his mistakes and try again in a different way.",author:"Dale Carnegie"},
{id:"280",quote:"The test for whether or not you can hold a job should not be the arrangement of your chromosomes.",author:"Bella Abzug"},
{id:"281",quote:"The thermometer of success is merely the jealousy of the malcontents.",author:"Salvador Dali"},
{id:"282",quote:"The thing always happens that you really believe in; and the belief in a thing makes it happen.",author:"Frank Loyd Wright"},
{id:"283",quote:"The toughest part of getting to the top of the ladder, is getting through the crowd at the bottom.",author:"Unknown"},
{id:"284",quote:"The toughest thing about success is that you've got to keep on being a success.",author:"Irving Berlin"},
{id:"285",quote:"The ultimate aim of the ego is not to see something, but to be something.",author:"Muhammed Iqbal"},
{id:"286",quote:"The very essence of leadership is that you have to have a vision.",author:"Theodore Hesburgh"},
{id:"287",quote:"The weak can never forgive. Forgiveness is the attribute of the strong.",author:"Mahatma Gandhi"},
{id:"288",quote:"The will to succeed is important, but what's more important is the will to prepare.",author:"Bobby Knight"},
{id:"289",quote:"The worst bankruptcy in the world is the person who has lost his enthusiasm.",author:"H. W. Arnold"},
{id:"290",quote:"There are no great people in this world, only great challenges which ordinary people rise to meet.",author:"William Frederick Halsy, Jr."},
{id:"291",quote:"There are two rules for success: 1) Never tell everything you know.",author:"Roger H. Lincoln"},
{id:"292",quote:"There are two ways of spreading light: to be the candle or the mirror that reflects it.",author:"Edith Wharton"},
{id:"293",quote:"There go my people.  I must find out where they are going so I can lead them.",author:"Alexandre Ledru Rollin"},
{id:"294",quote:"There is nothing deep down inside us except what we have put there ourselves.",author:"Richard Rorty"},
{id:"295",quote:"There is nothing worth the wear of winning, but laughter and the love of friends.",author:"James Boswell"},
{id:"296",quote:"There is only one person who could ever make you happy, and that person is you.",author:"David Burns"},
{id:"297",quote:"There is only one success - to be able to spend your life in your own way.",author:"Christopher Morley"},
{id:"298",quote:"There is real magic in enthusiasm. It spells the difference between mediocrity and accomplishment.",author:"Unknown"},
{id:"299",quote:"There isn't a person anywhere that isn't capable of doing more than he thinks he can.",author:"Henry Ford"},
{id:"300",quote:"They always say time changes things, but you actually have to change them yourself.",author:"Andy Warhol"},
{id:"301",quote:"They who dream by day are cognizant of many things which escape those who dream only by night.",author:"Edgar Allan Poe"},
{id:"302",quote:"Things may come to those who wait, but only things left by those who hustle.",author:"Abraham Lincoln"},
{id:"303",quote:"Things turn out best for people who make the best of the way things turn out.",author:"John Wooden"},
{id:"304",quote:"Those who have succeeded at anything and don't mention luck are kidding themselves.",author:"Larry King"},
{id:"305",quote:"Those who say it can't be done are being passed by those doing it.",author:"Unknown"},
{id:"306",quote:"To be wholly devoted to some intellectual exercise is to have succeeded in life.",author:"Robert Louis Stevenson"},
{id:"307",quote:"To know even one life has breathed easier because you have lived. This is to have succeeded.",author:"Ralph Waldo Emerson"},
{id:"308",quote:"To select well among old things, is almost equal to inventing new ones.",author:"Nicholas Charles Trublet"},
{id:"309",quote:"To succeed in life, you need two things: ignorance and confidence.",author:"Mark Twain"},
{id:"310",quote:"To succeed it is necessary to accept the world as it is and rise above it.",author:"Michael Korda"},
{id:"311",quote:"Too many people go through life waiting for things to happen instead of making them happen.",author:"Sahsa Azevedo"},
{id:"312",quote:"Too many people miss the silver lining because they're expecting gold.",author:"Maurice Seitter"},
{id:"313",quote:"True happiness involves the full use of one's power and talents.",author:"John W. Gardner"},
{id:"314",quote:"Try not to become a man of success but rather try to become a man of value.",author:"Albert Einstein"},
{id:"315",quote:"Wanting to be a success is aspiration. Doing something about it is perspiration.",author:"Unknown"},
{id:"316",quote:"We are all in the gutter, but some of us are looking at the stars.",author:"Oscar Wilde"},
{id:"317",quote:"We are still masters of our fate.We are still captains of our souls.",author:"Winston Churchill"},
{id:"318",quote:"We are what we repeatedly do. Excellence, therefore, is not an act but a habit.",author:"Aristotle"},
{id:"319",quote:"We can change our lives. We can do, have, and be exactly what we wish.",author:"Tony Robbins"},
{id:"320",quote:"We have to live today by what truth we can get today and be ready tomorrow to call it falsehood.",author:"William James"},
{id:"321",quote:"We must all hang together, or assuredly, we shall all hang separately.",author:"Benjamin Franklin"},
{id:"322",quote:"We should all start to live before we get too old. Fear is stupid. So are regrets.",author:"Marilyn Monroe"},
{id:"323",quote:"We should not let success go to our heads, or our failures go to our hearts.",author:"Unknown"},
{id:"324",quote:"We were young, but we had good advice and good ideas and lots of enthusiasm.",author:"Bill Gates"},
{id:"325",quote:"We would accomplish many more things if we did not think of them as impossible.",author:"C. Malesherbe s"},
{id:"326",quote:"What ever the mind of man can conceive and believe, it can achieve.",author:"Napolean Hill"},
{id:"327",quote:"What great thing would you attempt if you knew you could not fail?",author:"Robert H. Schuller"},
{id:"328",quote:"What lies behind us and what lies before us are tiny matters compared to what lies within us.",author:"Ralph Waldo Emerson"},
{id:"329",quote:"What oxygen is to the lungs, such is hope to the meaning of life.",author:"Emil Brunner"},
{id:"330",quote:"When I quote others I do so in order to express my own ideas more clearly.",author:"Michel de Montaigne"},
{id:"331",quote:"When the best things are not possible, the best may be made of those that are.",author:"Richard Hooker"},
{id:"332",quote:"When the world says, Give up, Hope whispers, 'Try it one more time.'",author:"Unknown"},
{id:"333",quote:"When you fail you learn from the mistakes you made and it motivates you to work even harder.",author:"Natalie Gulbis"},
{id:"334",quote:"When you feel like giving up, remember why you held on for so long in the first place.",author:"Unknown"},
{id:"335",quote:"When you reach the end of your rope, tie a knot in it and hang on.",author:"Thomas Jefferson"},
{id:"336",quote:"Whether you think you can or whether you think you can't, you're right.",author:"Henry Ford"},
{id:"337",quote:"Whoever is winning at the moment will always seem to be invincible.",author:"George Orwell"},
{id:"338",quote:"Winning is like shaving - you do it every day or you wind up looking like a bum.",author:"Jack Kemp"},
{id:"339",quote:"Winning is the most important thing in my life, after breathing. Breathing first, winning next.",author:"George Steinbrenner"},
{id:"340",quote:"Winning is the most important. Everything is consequence of that.",author:"Ayrton Senna"},
{id:"341",quote:"Winning isn't everything, but it beats anything that comes in second.",author:"Paul Bryant"},
{id:"342",quote:"Winning isn't worthwhile unless one has something finer and nobler behind it.",author:"Amos Alonzo Stagg"},
{id:"343",quote:"Winning may not be everything, but losing has little to recommend it.",author:"Dianne Feinstein"},
{id:"344",quote:"Work for something because it is good, not just because it stands a chance to succeed.",author:"Vaclav Havel"},
{id:"345",quote:"Worry does not empty tomorrow of its sorrow;it empties today of its strength.",author:"Unknown"},
{id:"346",quote:"Worrying is like a rocking chair, it gives you something to do, but it doesn't get you anywhere",author:"Unknown"},
{id:"347",quote:"You are always free to change your mind and choose a different future, or a different past.",author:"Richard Bach"},
{id:"348",quote:"You are never too old to set another goal or to dream a new dream.",author:"C. S. Lewis"},
{id:"349",quote:"You can't expect to hit the jackpot if you don't put a few nickels in the machine.",author:"Flip Wilson"},
{id:"350",quote:"You can't have a better tomorrow if you are always thinking about yesterday.",author:"Charles F. Kettering"},
{id:"351",quote:"You can't lead anyone else further than you have gone yourself. ",author:"Gene Mauch"},
{id:"352",quote:"You can't wait for inspiration. You have to go after it with a club.",author:"Jack London"},
{id:"353",quote:"You do not lead by hitting people over the head.  That's assault, not leadership.",author:"Dwight D. Eisenhower"},
{id:"354",quote:"You don't look out there for God, something in the sky, you look in you.",author:"Alan Watts"},
{id:"355",quote:"You have a very powerful mind that can make anything happen as long as you keep yourself centered.",author:"Dr. Wayne Dyer"},
{id:"356",quote:"You have succeeded in life when all you really want is only what you really need.",author:"Vernon Howard"},
{id:"357",quote:"You have to learn the rules of the game. And then you have to play better than anyone else.",author:"Albert Einstein"},
{id:"358",quote:"You know, when you run you got to be all in and you take risks of winning and losing.",author:"Jeb Bush"},
{id:"359",quote:"You need to overcome the tug of people against you as you reach for high goals.",author:"George S. Patton"},
{id:"360",quote:"You see things; and you say 'Why?' But I dream things that never were; and I say 'Why not?'",author:"George Bernard Shaw"},
{id:"361",quote:"You were not born a winner, and you were not born a loser. You are what you make yourself be.",author:"Lou Holtz"},
{id:"362",quote:"You will face many defeats in your life, but never let yourself be defeated.",author:"Maya Angelou"},
{id:"363",quote:"Your present circumstances don't determine where you can go;they merely determine where you start.",author:"Nido Qubein"},
{id:"364",quote:"Your work is first, learning is first, winning is everything because without it there is nothing.",author:"Orson Scott Card"},
{id:"365",quote:"Your work is first, learning is first, winning is everything because without it there is nothing.",author:"Orson Scott Card"},
{id:"366",quote:"Your work is first, learning is first, winning is everything because without it there is nothing.",author:"Orson Scott Card"}
];

document.write(Qoutes[day].quote +"<br/>"); 
document.write("- "+ Qoutes[day].author);

//-->
</script>
</table>

</body>
</html>
]]></Content>
</Module>
